Board of Governors fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Committees, 1968-2009; F-33-8
  - Audit Committee, 1995-2004; F-33-8-13; 25 cm of textual records; Simon Fraser University. Board of Governors. Audit Committee
    - Auditors selection sub-committee meeting minutes, 2004; F-33-8-13-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-179)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 1/2, 2004-2005; F-33-8-13-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-179)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 2/2, 2004-2005; F-33-8-13-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-179)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 1/2, 2006; F-33-8-13-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-179)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 2/2, 2006; F-33-8-13-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-179)
  - Academic Operations Committee, 1995-2006; F-33-8-14; 8.9 cm of textual records; Simon Fraser University. Board of Governors. Academic Operations Committee
    This sub-series consists of records created by the standing Academic Operations Committee. Responsibilities of the Committee encompassed the areas of academic administrative appointments; academic personnel; academic policy; faculty renewal plan; renewal, tenure, and promotion recommendations; as well as Senate Recommendations. Includes meeting agendas and minutes, reports, memos, correspondence, and terms of reference.
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 1995-2000; F-33-8-14-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-180)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 2001-2003; F-33-8-14-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-180)
    - Committee meeting minutes, 2003-2006; F-33-8-14-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-180)
    - Committee meeting minutes and correspondence, 2004-2005; F-33-8-14-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-180)
    - Committee meeting minutes and correspondence, 2006; F-33-8-14-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-180)
  - Finance and Administration Committee, 1995-2006; F-33-8-15; 17.6 cm of textual records; Simon Fraser University. Board of Governors. Finance and Administration Committee
    The Finance and Administration Committee was a standing committee responsible for ensuring adherence to Budget Policy Objectives, oversight of the University's financial operations and results, receival of reports on capital projects over 1.5 million, as well as receival of reports on adequacy and condition of capital assets. This sub-series contains records related to these responsibilities. Includes meeting agendas and minutes; reports; correspondence; and memos.
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 1995-2000; F-33-8-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-180)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 2001-2003; F-33-8-15-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-180)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 2001-2003; F-33-8-15-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-181)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 2004-2006; F-33-8-15-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-181)
    - Capital Finance Sub-committee meeting minutes and papers, 2002; F-33-8-15-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-181)
    - Working Group on Access Issues meeting agendas and papers 1/2, 2002-2004; F-33-8-15-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-181)
    - Working Group on Access Issues meeting agendas and papers 2/2, 2002-2004; F-33-8-15-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-181)
    - Working Group on Access Issues report and papers, 2003-2004; F-33-8-15-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-181)
    - Working Group on Access Issues meeting agendas, minutes and papers 1/2, 2004-2005; F-33-8-15-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-181)
    - Working Group on Access Issues meeting agendas, minutes and papers 2/2, 2004-2005; F-33-8-15-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-181)
    - Working Group on Access Issues meeting agendas, draft minutes and papers 1/2, 2004-2006; F-33-8-15-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-181)
    - Working Group on Access Issues meeting agendas, draft minutes and papers 2/2, 2004-2006; F-33-8-15-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-182)
  - Nominating Committee of the Board of Governors, 1998-2006; F-33-8-16; 1.6 cm of textual records; Simon Fraser University. Board of Governors. Nominating Committee of the Board of Governors
    This sub-series consists of records created by the Nominating Committee of the Board of Governors. This entity was a standing committee whose purpose was to receive nominations and make recommendations for Board approval of candidates for the position of Chair of the Board and Deputy Chair of the Board. The Committee was also responsible to recommend persons to sit as members on ad hoc committees. Includes meeting minutes and notes; correspondence; terms of reference; memos and a directory of Canadian Universities.
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 1998-2006; F-33-8-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-182)
  - Advancement Advisory Committee, 2001-2008; F-33-8-17; 4.7 cm of textual records; Simon Fraser University. Board of Governors. Advancement Advisory Committee
    This sub-series consists of records created by the Advancement Advisory Committee while advising on a broad range of advancement activities, including fundraising, alumni relationships, and special activities. Includes meeting agendas and minutes, reports, memos, correspondence, and terms of reference.
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 2001-2006; F-33-8-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-182)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 2007; F-33-8-17-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-182)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 2008; F-33-8-17-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-182)
  - Governance Working Group, 2004; F-33-8-18; 1.6 cm of textual records
    This sub-series consists of records related to the activities of the Governance Working Group. The final report and recommendations issued by this group resulted in the formation of the Governance Committee in July of 2004. Includes meeting agendas, memos, correspondence, and presentations.
    - Group meeting agendas and papers, 2004; F-33-8-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-182)
  - Governance Committee, 2004; F-33-8-19; 1.6 cm of textual records; Simon Fraser University. Board of Governors. Governance Committee
    This sub-series consists of records related to the activities of the Governance Committee. This Committee was formed in July 2004 as a result of a final report and recommendations provided by the Governance Working Group. The Governance Committee's responsibilities included regular review of Board Policy 10.01; ensuring effectiveness of the Board Orientation Strategy; monitoring University Governance trends; ensuring effective coordination with Board committees, Senate, and stakeholders; as well as evaluating the Board and making recommendations for improvement. Includes meeting agendas and minutes, terms of reference, recommendations, memos, correspondence, draft Board evaluation forms, reports, and best practice guidelines.
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers, 2004-2006; F-33-8-19-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-182)
  - Ad Hoc Advisory Committee on Media, Communications, Community, and Government Relations, 2005-2009; F-33-8-20; 14.1 cm of textual records, 1 CD-ROM (textual records), 1 enamel pin; Simon Fraser University. Board of Governors. Ad Hoc Advisory Committee on Media, Communications, Community, and Government Relations
    This sub-series consists of records created by the ad hoc committee that was formed to examine and improve the University's Media, Communications, Government, and Community Relations. The Committee was a precursor entity to the External Relations Committee. Includes meeting agendas, schedules, minutes, and notes; reports; presentations; promotional materials; and student surveys.
    Textual records; Textual records in electronic form (born-digital); Objects
    Includes 1 CD-ROM, located in file F-33-8-20-0-3; and 1 enamel pin, located in file F-33-8-20-0-2.
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 1/4, 2005-2007; F-33-8-20-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-182)
      Textual records; Objects; Records in electronic form (born-digital)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 2/4, 2005-2007; F-33-8-20-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-183)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 3/4, 2005-2007; F-33-8-20-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-183)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 4/4, 2005-2007; F-33-8-20-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-183)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 1/3, 2006-2009; F-33-8-20-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-183)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 2/3, 2006-2009; F-33-8-20-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-183)
    - Committee meeting agendas, minutes and papers 3/3, 2006-2009; F-33-8-20-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-183)
- Minute appendices and indexes, 1963-2006; F-33-9; 16.7 cm of textual records
  This series consists of indexes to the Board of Governors official minutes of regular meetings. The indexes are arranged chronologically. A list of all Members of the Board of Governors and details of each individual’s term; as well as a list of all Chancellors, Chairs of the Board, and Presidents from 1963-2000 are included at the beginning of the indexes.
  - Appendices to Minutes 1983-1985 1/2, F-33-9-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-110)
  - Appendices to Minutes 1983-1985 2/2, F-33-9-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-111)
  - Appendices to Minutes 1988-1992 1/2, F-33-9-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-111)
  - Appendices to Minutes 1988-1992 2/2, 1988-1982; F-33-9-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-111)
  - Indexes to Minutes 1963-1996 1/4, F-33-9-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-111)
  - Indexes to Minutes 1963-1996 2/4, F-33-9-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-111)
  - Indexes to Minutes 1963-1996 3/4, F-33-9-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-111)
  - Indexes to Minutes 1963-1996 4/4, F-33-9-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-111)
  - Indexes to Minutes 1999-2003, F-33-9-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-111)
  - Indexed Unsigned Minutes Copies 1999-2001, F-33-9-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-110)
- Meeting dockets, 2004-2008; F-33-10; 2.14 m of textual records
  This series comprises meeting dockets distributed to Board members, selected University officials, and campus organizations before each regular meeting, starting from 2004 onwards. The dockets include minutes from the previous meeting for approval, along with the current meeting agenda and all pertinent support papers.
  Includes meeting agendas, minutes, and support papers including correspondence; reports; financial statements; board committee minutes; contracts; architectural drawings; personnel records such as curriculum vitae, reference letters, and appointment forms; news clippings, and other documents.
  For minutes or agendas and support papers related to meetings held before 2004 when these records were kept separately, please refer to series [F-33-1: Official Minutes](f-33-1) and [F-33-2: Agenda support papers](f-33-2).
  - Board Month Docket January 2004 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-92)
  - Board Month Docket January 2004 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-92)
  - Board Month Docket March 2004 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-92)
  - Board Month Docket March 2004 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-93)
  - Board Month Docket May 2004 1/6, F-33-10-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-93)
  - Board Month Docket May 2004 2/6, F-33-10-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-93)
  - Board Month Docket May 2004 3/6, F-33-10-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-93)
  - Board Month Docket May 2004 4/6, F-33-10-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-93)
  - Board Month Docket May 2004 5/6, F-33-10-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-94)
  - Board Month Docket May 2004 6/6, F-33-10-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-94)
  - Board Month Docket July 2004 1/4, F-33-10-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-94)
  - Board Month Docket July 2004 2/4, F-33-10-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-94)
  - Board Month Docket July 2004 3/4, F-33-10-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-94)
  - Board Month Docket July 2004 4/4, F-33-10-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-94)
  - Board Month Docket September 2004 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 33-95)
  - Board Month Docket September 2004 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 33-95)
  - Board Month Docket November 2004 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 33-95)
  - Board Month Docket November 2004 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 33-95)
  - Board Month Docket November 2004 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 33-95)
  - Board Month Docket January 2005 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 33-95)
  - Board Month Docket January 2005 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 33-96)
  - Board Month Docket January 2005 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 33-96)
  - Board Month Docket March 2005 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 33-96)
  - Board Month Docket March 2005 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 33-96)
  - Board Month Docket March 2005 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 33-96)
  - Board Month Docket May 2005 1/6, F-33-10-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 33-96)
  - Board Month Docket May 2005 2/6, F-33-10-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 33-97)
  - Board Month Docket May 2005 3/6, F-33-10-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 33-97)
  - Board Month Docket May 2005 4/6, F-33-10-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 33-97)
  - Board Month Docket May 2005 5/6, F-33-10-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 33-97)
  - Board Month Docket May 2005 6/6, F-33-10-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 33-97)
  - Board Month Docket July 2005 1/4, F-33-10-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 33-97)
  - Board Month Docket July 2005 2/4, F-33-10-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 33-98)
  - Board Month Docket July 2005 3/4, F-33-10-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 33-98)
  - Board Month Docket July 2005 4/4, F-33-10-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 33-98)
  - Board Month Docket September 2005 1/4, F-33-10-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 33-98)
  - Board Month Docket September 2005 2/4, F-33-10-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 33-98)
  - Board Month Docket September 2005 3/4, F-33-10-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 33-98)
  - Board Month Docket September 2005 4/4, F-33-10-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 33-99)
  - Board Month Docket November 2005 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 33-99)
  - Board Month Docket November 2005 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 33-99)
  - Board Month Docket February 2006 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 33-99)
  - Board Month Docket February 2006 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 33-99)
  - Board Month Docket February 2006 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 33-100)
  - Board Month Docket March 2006 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 33-100)
  - Board Month Docket March 2006 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 33-100)
  - Board Month Docket May 2006 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 33-100)
  - Board Month Docket May 2006 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 33-100)
  - Board Month Docket May 2006 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 33-101)
  - Board Month Docket July 2006 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 33-101)
  - Board Month Docket July 2006 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 33-101)
  - Board Month Docket September 2006 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 33-101)
  - Board Month Docket September 2006 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 33-101)
  - Board Month Docket November 2006 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 33-102)
  - Board Month Docket November 2006 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 33-102)
  - Board Month Docket November 2006 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 33-102)
  - Board Month Docket January 2007 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 33-102)
  - Board Month Docket January 2007 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 33-102)
  - Board Month Docket March 2007 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 33-103)
  - Board Month Docket March 2007 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 33-103)
  - Board Month Docket March 2007 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 33-103)
  - Board Month Docket May 2007 1/5, F-33-10-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 33-103)
  - Board Month Docket May 2007 2/5, F-33-10-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 33-103)
  - Board Month Docket May 2007 3/5, F-33-10-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 33-104)
  - Board Month Docket May 2007 4/5, F-33-10-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 33-104)
  - Board Month Docket May 2007 5/5, F-33-10-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 33-104)
  - Board Month Docket July 2007 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 33-104)
  - Board Month Docket July 2007 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 33-104)
  - Board Month Docket July 2007 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 33-104)
  - Board Month Docket September 2007 1/4, F-33-10-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 33-105)
  - Board Month Docket September 2007 2/4, F-33-10-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 33-105)
  - Board Month Docket September 2007 3/4, F-33-10-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 33-105)
  - Board Month Docket September 2007 4/4, F-33-10-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 33-105)
  - Board Month Docket November 2007 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 33-105)
  - Board Month Docket November 2007 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 33-106)
  - Board Month Docket November 2007 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 33-106)
  - Board Month Docket January 2008 1/4, F-33-10-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 33-106)
  - Board Month Docket January 2008 2/4, F-33-10-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 33-106)
  - Board Month Docket January 2008 3/4, F-33-10-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 33-106)
  - Board Month Docket January 2008 4/4, F-33-10-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 33-106)
  - Board Month Docket March 2008 1/3, F-33-10-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 33-107)
  - Board Month Docket March 2008 2/3, F-33-10-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 33-107)
  - Board Month Docket March 2008 3/3, F-33-10-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 33-107)
  - Board Month Docket April 2008 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 33-107)
  - Board Month Docket April 2008 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 33-107)
  - Board Month Docket May 2008 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 33-107)
  - Board Month Docket May 2008 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 33-107)
  - Board Month Docket June 2008, F-33-10-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 33-108)
  - Board Month Docket July 2008 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 33-108)
  - Board Month Docket July 2008 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 33-108)
  - Board Month Docket September 2008 1/4, F-33-10-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 33-108)
  - Board Month Docket September 2008 2/4, F-33-10-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 33-109)
  - Board Month Docket September 2008 3/4, F-33-10-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 33-109)
  - Board Month Docket September 2008 4/4, F-33-10-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 33-109)
  - Board Month Docket November 2008 1/2, F-33-10-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 33-109)
  - Board Month Docket November 2008 2/2, F-33-10-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 33-109)
- Board Retreats and Strategy Sessions, 1994-2007; F-33-11; 23.7 cm of textual records, 1 CD-ROM (ppt)
  This series consists of records created during the planning and facilitation of retreat events attended by Board executives and members. The retreats involved socializing and networking, discussing issues and concerns relevant to the Board, reflection on University events and priorities, as well as strategic planning. Includes retreat agendas and notes, memos, invoices, reports, presentations, correspondence, evaluation forms, event facility brochures, articles, speaker bios, and maps.
  Textual records; Multiple media
  Includes 1 CD-ROM, located in file F-33-11-0-11.
  - Retreat agenda and papers Jan. 1994, F-33-11-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-184)
  - Retreat agenda and papers Oct. 1994, F-33-11-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-184)
  - Retreat agenda and papers Apr. 1995, F-33-11-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-184)
  - Retreat agenda and papers Dec. 1995, F-33-11-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-184)
  - Retreat agenda and papers Oct. 1996, F-33-11-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-184)
  - Retreat agenda and papers Oct. 1997, F-33-11-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-184)
  - Retreat and Strategy Session Docket Oct. 1998, F-33-11-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-109)
  - Retreat and Strategy Session Docket Oct. 1999, F-33-11-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-109)
  - Retreat and Strategy Session Docket Jun. 2001, F-33-11-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-109)
  - Retreat and Strategy Session Docket Jul. 2002, F-33-11-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-110)
  - Retreat and Strategy Session Docket Jun. 2003, F-33-11-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-110)
    Textual records; Multi-media
  - Retreat and Strategy Session Docket Jun. 2004, F-33-11-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-110)
  - Retreat and Strategy Session Docket Jun. 2005, F-33-11-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-110)
  - Retreat and Strategy Session Docket Jun. 2007, F-33-11-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-184)